https://www.riverside-golf.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at info@riverside.com.
This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.riverside.com and how it used.
Log Files
Like many other Websites, www.riverside.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.
Cookies and Web Beacons
www.riverside.com does not use cookies.
DoubleClick DART Cookie
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.riverside.com.
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.riverside.com and other sites on the internet.
User's may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include .... Google AdSense
These third party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.riverside.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, Javascript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.
www.riverside.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.riverside.com
Sign up to receive our newsletter
Golf
Club House
Packages
News
Gallery
Membership
Contact Us
© 2020. Riverside Golf Club. ALL RIGHT RESERVED managed by PT. Gitamaya Inter Buana
